(Penny:)Another night?
(Penny:)Well, I guess you can try...
(Penny:)...but deep inside your heart you'll know
that laundry night is always Saturday night.
(Sheldon:)Woman, you are playing with forces
beyond your ken.
(Penny:)Yeah, well,
your Ken can kiss my Barbie.
(Leonard:)Sheldon?
Sheldon? Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Yes?
(Penny:)Where are my clothes?
- Your clothes?
- Yes. I left them in the washers.
I went to get them,
they were gone.
Really? Despite the sign that says:
"Do not leave laundry unattended"?
(Penny:)Sheldon, where are my clothes?
(Sheldon:)You know, I do recall
seeing some female undergarments.
(Sheldon:)Where was that? Oh, yes.
(Sheldon:)Earlier this evening...